<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interalia</title>
    <link>https://interalia.host/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on interalia</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://interalia.host/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/imprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;address&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;Address&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;interalia gGmbH&#xA;Rehlingstraße 9&#xA;79100 Freiburg i. Brsg.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@interalia.host&#34; &gt;hello@interalia.host&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registery No.:&lt;/strong&gt; HRB 731271, Amtsgericht Freiburg im Breisgau&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CEO&lt;/strong&gt;: Kristina Klein, Paula Grünwald&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical&lt;/strong&gt;: Hugo Static Site Generator with DecapCMS&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exclusion-of-liability&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;Exclusion of liability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the context of this website in accordance with § 55 section 2 RStV is the respective author.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-liability&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;Content liability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The contents of our website were created with the utmost care. However, we cannot guarantee the accuracy, completeness and timeliness of the content. As a service provider, we are responsible for our own content on our website in accordance with § 7 para.1 TMG under the general laws. According to § 8 to 10 TMG, we are not obligated to monitor transmitted or stored information or to investigate circumstances that indicate illegal activity. Obligations to remove or block the use of information according to general laws remain unaffected. However, liability in this regard is only possible from the point in time at which a concrete infringement of the law becomes known. If we become aware of such infringements, we will remove this content immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;interalia operates the website accessible on the Internet at &lt;a href=&#34;https://interalia.host/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;https://interalia.host&lt;/a&gt; and its respective subdirectories (hereinafter “interalia.host” or the “Website”).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this privacy policy, interalia would like to explain to you which data is processed in which form when you visit our website. This also fulfills our obligation to inform you in accordance with Article 13 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-personal-data-purposes-and-legal-basis-of-data-processing&#34;&gt;I. Personal data, purposes and legal basis of data processing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;personal-data&#34;&gt;Personal data&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the GDPR, personal data means “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/service/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>interalia Strategy 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/reports/interalia-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/reports/interalia-strategy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-vision&#34;&gt;Our vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We dream of a well-resourced, diverse civil society ecosystem, able to grow, thrive and hold power to account.&lt;/strong&gt; To make that possible, we dream of a network of fiscal hosts, providing a shared infrastructure of operational support, knowledge and resources, which strengthens the resilience of the civil society ecosystem, transforming our relationships with each other to be centred around care instead of competition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our mission&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;interalia enables and empowers members of civil society working at the intersection of tech and social justice to advance their core missions, by taking care of their operations and finances as they evolve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Fiscal Hosting?</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/reports/what-is-fiscal-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/reports/what-is-fiscal-hosting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fiscal hosting, or fiscal sponsorship&lt;/strong&gt;, is where a legally registered organisation (the host, or sponsor) holds and manages funds on behalf of someone else. By doing so they take fiscal responsibility (and often legal responsibility) for what happens with those funds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, people typically say ‘fiscal sponsorship’; in other parts of the world, ‘fiscal host’ seems to be more common. We at interalia generally say ‘fiscal hosting’.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://interalia.host/en/reports/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://interalia.host/en/reports/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re interalia –a new fiscal host, registered as a non-profit (gGmbH) in Germany. We’re focused on supporting the broad ecosystem of civil society working at the intersection of tech and social justice, by taking care of their operations and finances as they evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We were founded in mid-2024 by Paula Grünwald, Kristina Klein and Zara Rahman, and after almost a year of behind-the-scenes setting up our infrastructure, developing our strategy and building out our processes, we’re excited to launch publicly today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
